<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Moe Serifu</title>
    <link>http://www.moeserifu.moe/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Moe Serifu</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 11:09:03 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
        <atom:link href="http://www.moeserifu.moe/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>First Board Meeting</title>
      <link>http://www.moeserifu.moe/posts/2018-01-12-first-board-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jan 2018 11:09:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.moeserifu.moe/posts/2018-01-12-first-board-meeting/</guid>
      <description>The circle has officially begun to spin the wheels of progress! Just this week, Moe Serifu Circle held its first meeting of the Board of Directors. It&amp;rsquo;s been a great few months with people coming seemingly out of the woodwork to volunteer their services towards making Masa-chan a real application.
This first meeting had us discussing a variety of exciting topics for the near future of the circle. The long and short of it is that we are on a timeline to have all of our business paperwork in within the next month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website Is Live</title>
      <link>http://www.moeserifu.moe/posts/2017-10-25-website-is-live/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 07:22:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.moeserifu.moe/posts/2017-10-25-website-is-live/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As of today, the Moe Serifu Agent project website has gone live! We are now up
and running at the oh-so-cute .moe TLD, and with our new URL we now have a place
to slap on project promotions. We&amp;rsquo;re now going be jumping right in to that as
we launch our first promotion campaigns. Just in time, too; we have our first
recruitment presentation tomorrow!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site Creation</title>
      <link>http://www.moeserifu.moe/posts/2017-10-16-site-creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Oct 2017 06:51:57 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.moeserifu.moe/posts/2017-10-16-site-creation/</guid>
      <description>At this point, the first unit of work on the main website is complete. The primary design is finished, and now we only need to do a bit more work on the supplementary pages. The good news is that all of this can now be done without further work from high-powered graphics programs.
To be completely honest, this post is intended as a test for the upcoming blog pages and index.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
